(Penny:)So what other annoying habits
shall we discuss?
(Sheldon:)Uh, we don't
discuss anything.
(Sheldon:)Leonard is the signatory
to the roommate agreement.
(Sheldon:)As such, he bears
responsibility
(Sheldon:)for all your infractions
and must pay all fines.
(Leonard:)Fines?
Yes.
(Sheldon:)If Penny's going to be
spending nights here again,
(Sheldon:)you'll need to set up
an escrow account.
(Sheldon:)Sign here.
(Raj:)Hello, Hawaii.
(Raj:)This is Dr. Koothrappali
in Pasadena.
(Raj:)I'd like you to reposition
the telescope, please.
(Raj:)Scarlett Johansson's house!
(Raj:)I'm kidding, Hawaii.
(Raj:)Mahalo.
(Raj:)Whoo!
(Howard:)It might have
been a mistake
(Howard:)to open that second
bottle of wine.
(Bernadette:)Well, live and learn.
(Bernadette:)So, Raj, do you think this
planet you're looking for
(Bernadette:)could have an atmosphere
that supports life?
(Howard:)Maybe.
(Raj:)If it did, I'd be famous.
(Raj:)I'd be on the cover
of magazines.